{
    "id": "bd53ab6d12394d71bf641a961b221339",
    "title": "Simple Present Or Present Perfect Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I .....................… an old friend of mine yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "meet",
                "met",
                "have met"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ..................... all the plays of Shakespeare.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "read",
                "have read",
                "had read"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She ...................... in two films.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "acted",
                "has acted",
                "have acted"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ....................... a ghost.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "saw",
                "see",
                "have seen"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………….. to help him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "refused",
                "refuses",
                "has refused"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………. home early.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "leave",
                "left",
                "has left"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Janet ...................... me a story the other day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "told",
                "have told",
                "tells"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Maya and her family ...................... to Chicago last year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "move",
                "moved",
                "moves"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ..................... anything from them since then.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "not hear",
                "have not heard",
                "did not hear"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………….. that he would not do it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "says",
                "said",
                "say"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Amir said nothing when he ………………. the news.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "heard",
                "have heard",
                "has heard"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}